How y'all doing?
>> Good. How are you, man? Good.
>> Jonathan, what was this process like for
you? Obviously, there were rumors about
you potentially moving. Uh, I know there
were some cap issues. You seem to be
happy there. Um, how has this whole sort
of situation developed for you?
>> Yeah. Um, it's been a I guess you could
say challenge, not challenging, but um,
on top of rehab, um, I just had my son
um, at the end of January. Um it was a
lot up in the air, but um ultimately I
knew there was gonna be an end goal and
I knew we're going to eventually get to
the bottom of it. Um I'm just glad now
that we're at the end of it. Now I can
just worry about football. So um glad to
be here, man. This is one of the best u
organizations that I can remember since
coming up watching um football knowing,
understanding their history behind it.
Um and to be a part of organization like
this is is uh means a lot to me.
>> How is your shoulder? Are you still
rehabbing?
>> Yeah. Um on a sore plan, but ultimately
I feel good. I mean uh they they don't
want me to say it, but if we had to
play, I could play. So, um, but
ultimately, man, I I feel good. I'm in a
good spot. Um, and coming here with the
best trainers as well and the best docs
here and stuff like that. I know I'm in
good hands.
>> What's your thoughts on how you fit in
with the defensive line with the
interior guys and also the edge ro on
this roster?
>> Yeah. Um, I mean, if you look at it
across the board, man, they got some
dogs already. You starting interior
wise, you know, um, JMO. Um, and
obviously, you know, JC and, you know,
JD, they going to do their things. Um,
and on the edge guys, man, it's just
such a young presence and guys are just
relentless. And um and I feel like
that's where I can add to is just a vet
presence. Um you know, you got Nolan
already doing his thing already and and
elevating his game to that point. Jix as
well. Um you know, AK I already know
about him training him before and then
Joe coming in as well. All these guys
are just hungry. Um and I think that you
know adding my little expertise and
still bringing my relentless um energy
and my effort to the game and polishing
up my certain techniques as well cuz I'm
still learning too just cuz I'm the vet.
I feel like I still got a long way to go
as far as um polishing up my technique.
But just adding to what is already being
put here um is is something I want to
bring to the table. I'm not going to
change anything up, change anything I do
by myself. Um I'm just going to play
ball and keep doing what I've been doing
since I've been in the league.
>> You take pride in that being being the
veteran voice in in a room like this?
Yeah, I was just talking um Matt earlier
um and and just talking about like now
as I've always been a younger one in the
room uh or always hung around vets uh
coming up and to be a vet now it's still
kind of like weird to say they call you
uncle and I'm like I'm only 28 but um
but stuff like that man I take pride in
that because ultimately um you're you're
working towards something that's bigger
than you ultimately you know that this
league obviously you got your your short
time here or whatever the time period
may be um as as many people I can affect
um whether it's on the football field or
off the football field. Um that that's
where I find joy at and you know
whenever we're on the same page and
we're all you know trending towards that
the same goal um that's when I feel like
we're at our best. So anywhere I can uh
help contribute to that I'm here.
>> What's been your impression of Vic Panio
so far and how do you view yourself as a
fit in in his scheme?
>> Yeah. Um Vic is we all know he's a
mastermind of calling plays and and and
scheming things up. Um and also knowing
when to just let it fly and just play
normal uh straight rush four. Um, and I
feel like that's a great addition or
I'll be a great addition to this cuz I
mean I don't know how he's going to draw
it up. That's the exciting part about
it. Um, but I know when it is uh drawn
up, it's going to be something serious
and we're going to be a force to be
working with. So, um, anyway I can be
disruptive, bring that relentless motor
still here and continue to do what I've
been doing. Um, I'll fit right in.
>> Jonathan, 12 and a half sacks here last
year in Houston, 12 sacks your first
year in Minnesota, and then three last
year. What do you make of your season?
Why do you think the sacks didn't come
last year?
>> Um, I mean, I think a couple times, I
mean, I had guys on my grasps in my
arms. Um think just probably lowering
the center uh my target at times and
most I'm trying to go for the ball, go
for the kill shot or something like
that. And um eyes get big at times. I
think a lot of stuff goes into that. But
um I still feel like I rush well. I
still feel like I was still getting back
there. I feel like my moves didn't drop
off at all. Um I always tell myself,
listen, the day somebody got to tell me
to get to the quarterback, that's why no
need to hang it up. But um outside of
that, if my issue was wrapping a guy up,
I promise you I'm going be in good spot.
So um if anybody want to let a
quarterback go free this time, be more
than free.
>> Well, sorry. you mentioned still wanting
to improve parts of your game
technique-wise. Where what what's next
for you in your mind?
>> Yeah. Um elevating that. I feel like as
you mentioned before, I'm sorry. Um
having 12 and 12 and then obviously I
had the down year and that was not to my
standard by any means. Um I'm coming for
more. Um definitely trying to get back
to that point of double digits to where
I can affect the game. And obviously
it's not necessarily all about me
getting back to double digits. It's more
so how can we affect the quarterback? If
I get the quarterback down, cool. Um
everybody know that's the intention.
That's the goal and the mindset as soon
as that ball is snapped. Um, if somebody
else, let's say Nolan or JC or JD get
it, I'm more than happy. It's the same.
It's a sack to me in my mind. Um, but as
long as we affecting the game, I promise
you, we going to be in a good spot.
>> This contract and
>> Oh, what's up? I a seen a long way since
season. Uh, so to reflect on uh what's
brought you here throughout the years,
what what do you reflect on whenever you
reach this stage of your career and
what's ahead of you?
>> Yeah. Um when you look at the guys like
you know BG um you know um Chris Long
you know um I say guys even like Derek
Barnett you know Sweat all these guys
have been here before um you just try to
just add on to what they've already
built here. I mean they you have so many
greats have played here um done great
things um not just on the football field
but in the community um something that's
up my alley that I love to you know be a
part of the community and still love to
play football at the same time. I feel
like I fit right in with that. Um, I
respect the hell out of the the guys
that have come before me and all I can
do is just continue to just carry that
light. Um, and make sure that what they
think the things they've done in the
past doesn't go in vain. So, um, I love
everything about it. I love the historic
franchise. Um, I'm want to be a part of
that. I want to be a part of having some
hardware in my finger. That's that's
literally the main thing of of of one of
the things I knew watching growing up is
that's something I want to be a part of.
>> As far as as far as the trade is
concerned, when did you kind of get an
inkling that something like this could
happen? And then what were the last few
days like as far as you know coming in
getting your physical and also um the
contract and everything?
>> Yeah. Um I mean I think steam probably
picked up last couple days probably
recently probably a day or so. Um just
cuz we speculations will be out there
but I'm the type of person in my agents
as well where we don't really deal with
speculation. We just like listen if it
gets concrete or close that possibly
happen then we'll actually give a little
energy to it. But um my whole time I I
was a Viking until otherwise and then
now I'm an eagle. So, um, I loved every
second. Soon as I got that call from
agent and that said it's it's going
through, I hopped on the flight as fast
as I could.
>> We're in this league for uh for
someone's third contract to be the
biggest one yet. What have you done
these past two years to kind of get to
the level you're at right now?
>> Man, the same things I've been doing.
Um, just continuously grinding,
understanding that um
there's another level to be unlocked.
And I feel like that's when as soon as
you get complacent in this league, it's
an innovative league. As soon as you get
complacent, you get passed up. Um and
and despite obviously whatever the sack
totals, whatever stuff may be, I still
affected the game um in the run game. Um
I still was able to get double digits
TFL as no one talks about that. Um but I
pride myself on stopping that run so I
can get to the opportunity to rest the
passer and um that's what that's the
main thing I'm trying to get everybody
else to do as well. Um and bring to the
table as far as the D line to be
relentless in all all aspects of the
game because um we all the sacks and all
look good, but you know, if you're
getting the ball ran down your throat, I
mean you got to you got to tighten up.
So, um, that's the main thing is
stopping the run so we can get to that
point. And I'm just proud of myself on
doing the dirty work till it's time to
shine.
>> You mentioned you're the vet now and you
know how we mentioned team captain. How
important is the the leadership part of
it? How important is that to you bring
others up?
>> Yeah. Um, just because I was one of
those young guys that was kind of, you
know, not necessarily nervous to say
something, but you know, when you don't
make enough plays or you don't, you
know, um, have the name at certain
times, you feel like you don't have a
voice in this league. And I understand
that. listen, you're just as much of a
pro as everybody else is in his room.
So, um, having somebody like that myself
where I'll ask the uncomfortable
questions. I'll ask a question that he
probably doesn't want to ask because he
feels like it's going to be
embarrassing. Um, but I learned real
quick if you're going to have that guy
standing next to you on the on on the
lines on the field and he doesn't know
what's going on. Um, that's on you and
we can't keep going with the whole
mindset of figuring it out or you're a
young guy, earn your earn your share,
earn your keep. Obviously, we know
that's a standard, but um, at times
there's a time and place where we got to
add on and and help them out a little
bit. And I think that that's the part
where um you're only as strong as your
weakest link. So I carry that on um
since I've been in the league and that's
why I've always been a guy to easily
talk to certain guys or um just convey
it in a way that it gets through and
resonates with them easier as opposed to
the oldfashioned hey do this, do this
and that. Just break it down to a
different way till we're all on the same
page. And if we're all on the same page
and on the same mindset uh yeah like I
keep saying we're going to be a force.
>> You were at the Sixers game last night.
What what have been your impressions
both in your own experience like lived
experience over the last 48 hours of
Philly fans and the city and then also
just through talking to players who have
played here or through playing here
yourself?
>> Sure. Um first I've never played in you
know Lincoln at all. I've never played
in the um stadium at all. I came here
for preseason game last year but um I've
never played in the um in the stadium.
So that's something I really look
forward to. So to only get a taste of
what you know the Sixers game was last
night and man they they lost but that
was a crazy environment. I mean I was
just at the Hawks game back home in
Georgia just looking at that and
comparing the two. I was just like man
this environment was way way way better.
Um no disrespect to them but ultimately
man it's it's different up here and and
they take pride of it. They take pride
in everything they do and that's it's a
blue bluecollar city. Um when you work
your tail off everything is just going
to be um you know rewarded back to you.
um they're just passionate and and and I
love that ultimately. Um they want one
thing and this is why why not we want
the same thing. So um I carry that um on
my chip on my shoulder. Um I respect the
hell out of this city, respect the hell
out of this or I just definitely um
understand what putting this jersey on,
putting this helmet on um actually means
to this city and I'm I'm going to take
pride in that.
>> What's it been like? What's it been like
having a being a father for a second
time and having a son for the first
time?
>> Uh well I have a 2-year-old. She's a
daughter. She's my daughter and uh I've
been going through it. So she's them
terrible tools ain't no joke. Um but you
know having my son man it definitely put
it in different perspective. Um I always
say my girls always going to have me
attached to the hip. She going to get
whatever she want but them boys is it's
a little different. Um my dad um he
passed when I was in my junior year high
school. Um and my stepdad passing like
my first my second year in the league.
Um so you know doing this father thing
now is I would say it's kind of on my
own. Um, but it's it's such a rewarding
feeling to where um, you know, when you
see the kids smile, you know you're
doing something right. Um, something
that you probably don't have right next
to you is your dad in your ear saying,
"Hey, do this and that for your son or
do this and that for your daughter." Um,
but my mom has been a tremendous help in
that aspect. Um, obviously she going to
do so much. She's not a man. But, um, I
think I just take pride in that. Um,
seeing the smiles on their faces. Um,
everything I do is for them. Um, and it
just, like I said, just give me a new
outlook on life and give me some more
harder to work for. you think back pre-
agency two years ago, the Eagles were
looking at edge ruters then. Is this a
team that was on your radar? Were there
were there thoughts this this could have
happened before?
>> Uh, it definitely was on my radar for
sure. Um,
like I said, I got to make no mistakes,
so uh I don't know what what went happen
then, but we here now.
>> You uh obviously played Minnesota and
Chris Cooper is now the offensive line
coach here.
>> So, I wonder what it was like working
against him and and what we can expect
to see from him here. Yeah, Coupe is a a
very detailed guy. I think that's one of
the things people miss is just the
attention to details that he knows about
individual rushers. I mean, I would go
to him literally asking him, "Hey, yo,
like how would you block a guy like me
in practice?" And I just asking little
things and bouncing ideas off of him.
Um, and you can see it through the
players and how they talk. You know,
when I was in Minnesota, just talking to
the offensive lineman there and they all
talk the same way. They talk with the
same um, you know, the same jargon. They
always um, have a very, very detailed
plan of every week they go into
something. And I think that that's
something um, he's going to bring to the
table. And I love Coupe. I mean, he's
been a good guy. And usually I hate
offensive line coaches. So, um, but he's
he's a good guy. And I think when you
can have that relationship to where
we're going to go ahead and we're going
to go at it. You may see us cussing each
other out during practice and stuff like
that, but we all on the same goal and we
all understand that, you know, when it's
time to step between these white lines
and we we have a job to do. And, um, I
think he's definitely fit for the job. I
I can't wait to see what he does with
this group. Um, he already got some
great guys already to start with it. So,
he's going to come into it with a
really, really good uh let's say some
good food on his plate.
>> Thanks, John.
>> Appreciate it.